Analytical Cookbook for Sigma-Based Benchmarking
Welcome to this session on benchmarking.
What we got in front of us here, is a little instrument off of a machine somewhere.
It looks like it's measuring temperature on a machine.
Well, it’s really kind of interesting because our business is kinda the same way.
Wouldn't it be nice if we had a gauge we can plug into our business
to say how good we're doing? Like, right about here,
it says you're doing average.
Or maybe if the needle was over here, it would say that your
world-class. So, what we’d like to have is a little measuring device,
that can tell us when we’re getting better and when we’re getting worse over time.
Well, the Sigma scale is an easy way to do that.
So, imagine on this scale that this was one sigma, two sigma, three sigma,
four sigma, five sigma, six sigma, and seven sigma, and so on as the
counter goes around here. Wouldn’t that be cool. Well, we can do that. A simple way is this.
Simply convert it directly to Sigma using a conversion table.
It's that simple that I can go from observed error rate
to Sigma capability, and that's my benchmark.
Thank you for choosing SSMI.